Hey.
I'm so happy you're still here.
We finished a new chapter.
So let's recap what we've learned in this one.
First, Decibel is a unit that has to represent a ratio and power.
It prevents to use very small or very large values.
And it transforms multiplications into sums and divisions into subtractions.
The RSSI is the received power, and if the RSSI is above the receiver sensitivity, the transmission
is successful.
Next, we saw that the SNR is the ratio between the signal under noise.
The Link Budget evaluates the potential of the transmission and we saw Real Link Budget Values for two different
lower transceiver.
And finally, when digging into the documentation, we found out that changing the spreading factor
hold your chance to reception capacities.
We spoke about being able of receiving a signal drawn in a noise 100 times stronger than the signal itself.
But changing the spreading factor has also an influence on the bitrate.
And that's what we're going to see in the next chapter.